frenchtoast.com 2019-04-02

# Privacy Policy & Security | French Toast School Uniforms | French Toast

Untitled Document

**Privacy and Security**

Last Updated: January 7, 2019

French Toast School Uniforms, LT Apparel and our affiliates (our “Company”) have created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and security. The following privacy policy describes our practices for collecting, using, sharing, disclosing and managing the personal information we collect at our website: [http://www.frenchtoast.com](http://www.frenchtoast.com/) or when you otherwise contact us offline or that one of our affiliates may receive to process electronic payment information.  

**Privacy of Children**  
Our Company is committed to protecting the privacy of children. This site is intended for a general audience, and is not directed or intended for use by children under the age of 13. We do not collect personally identifiable information from any person we actually know is a child under the age of 13. If our Company learns that a child under the age of 13 has provided personal information to our site, we will take steps to remove such information from our records. If you are a parent or guardian that has knowledge that we have collected information from your child, please contact us to request removal at service@frenchtoast.com.  

**How is my information collected and used?**   
When we use the term “Personal Information”, we mean information that can or could be used to identify you individually as a person. This may include when you use our website, register for an account, make a purchase, sign up for our email lists, participate in in our promotions or school fundraising events, [product review, surveys, etc.]  or otherwise contact or communicate with us. Our Company collects information from you when you choose to share it with our website. The Personal Information we collect may include your name, billing and/or shipping information, telephone number, email address, IP address,  
Examples of the categories of Personal Information we collect from you and use are further outlined below:  

**Information You Provide**  
We use Personal Information which you share with us, for example, in the following ways:

  * **Make a Purchase**. If you purchase from our site, we collect payment information from you.  Depending on the form of payment, this may include credit or debit card information, shipping and transaction details, which our Company uses to fulfill your orders.
  * **Interactions through Social Media**. You may interact with our content on or through third party social networking sites such as Facebook, Twitter, YouTube or Pinterest.
  * **Customer Reviews, Live Chat and other Public Forums**. Our site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. When you submit identifiable comments or content on our site, we use this information to communicate with you or otherwise for the purpose of the submission. Please be aware that any photos or comments that you submit on a public forum will become accessible by the public.
  * **Promotions**. We will send you information regarding new additions to our site and special promotions if you select to receive our promotions by email.

**Information Automatically Collected**   
Our website gathers certain information automatically and stores it in our log files, such as your IP address and action of each visitor. We use Personal Information for error tracking, to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website or otherwise in accordance with our Privacy Policy. Your IP address is used, for example, to help identify you and your shopping cart.  
We use various data collection methods to collect other types of data that do not directly reveal your identity. This aggregated or anonymized information such as what pages are visited, is used by us to improve the content of our website, our products and / or our services.   

**Cookies**   
Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and for other purposes. You have the option of setting your browser to reject cookies. However, if our cookie is rejected, we will not be able to keep items in your shopping cart and you will not be able to complete your order online. For you to complete your order, you must allow our Company to use a cookie.  
Our website's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like your name and email address) and unique identifiers (like your password). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Unique identifiers (such as passwords) are collected to verify the user's identity and for use as account numbers in our record system.  
Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (such as their email address). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about our company, to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.  
When we ask for your email address, we give you these options:  

**Email me promotions.**  

We will send you information regarding new additions to our site and special promotions. If you select this option, we will also use email to contact you regarding an order you have placed with our Company.  

**Email me nothing.**  

We will send you an email receipt for your order, but nothing else.  
We will only use a telephone number you supply us with to contact you regarding an order that you have placed with our Company. We will not call you regarding promotions and we will not share your phone number with a third party, except under certain circumstances, see the Information Sharing With Others section below   
When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, address and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners. We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to our website, new Company services and special offers we think you'll find valuable.  

**Will FrenchToast.com disclose the information it collects to outside parties?**   
Our Company  does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others; see the choice/opt-out section below; our Company may disclose your information to third parties under certain circumstances; see the Information Sharing With Others section below.  

**Security**   
Our Company has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information provided to us. We utilize industry standard encryption processes and methods to safeguard your Personal Information during our online checkout process. However, no transmission of information over the Internet can be guaranteed. As a result, while we are committed to protecting your information, we cannot guarantee the security of any Personal Information that you transmit to us on or through our website.  

**Your Communication Choices and Opt Out Rights**   
Our website provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. You can send email to service@frenchtoast.com. (If you use more than one e-mail address to shop with us, send this message from each e-mail account you use.)  
You can send mail to the following postal address:  
French Toast School Uniforms,  
321 Herrod Blvd.,  
Dayton, NJ 08810.  
You can call the following telephone number: 1-800-FRENCHTOAST (1-800-373-6248).  

**Correcting and Updating Your Information**   
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. You can send email to service@frenchtoast.com. (If you use more than one e-mail address to shop with us, send this message from each e-mail account you use.)  
You can send mail to the following postal address:  
French Toast School Uniforms,  
321 Herrod Blvd.,  
Dayton, NJ 08810.  
You can call the following telephone number: 1-800-FRENCHTOAST (1-800-373-6248).  

**Information Sharing with Others**  
_Affiliates and Business Successors_  
We may share your information with our affiliates, partners, subsidiaries, business partners or in connection with a sale or merger or similar transfer of our business.  
_Service Providers_  
We may share Personal Information with our service providers who perform certain services on our behalf, such as for example our payment processors or accountants.    
_Legal Matters_  
We may disclose Personal Information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to respond to judicial orders or government requests and investigations or as otherwise required or permitted by applicable law. We may disclose your information if we determine it is necessary in order to protect your and / or our safety and /or the security of our website, servers, network systems, databases or in the course of investigating a breach of contract or violation or potential violation of law. We may also disclose your information if we believe that there has been a violation of our terms and conditions or other contractual agreements or to enforce our legal rights or those of a third party.   

**How to Contact Us**   
If you have any questions about, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us via the following methods: You can send email to privacy@frenchtoast.com. (If you use more than one e-mail address to shop with us, send this message from each e-mail account you use.)

You can send mail to the following postal address:  
French Toast School Uniforms  
321 Herrod Blvd.  
Dayton, NJ 08810  
You can call the following telephone number: 1-800-FRENCHTOAST (1-800-373-6248).
